A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 340)
  - General Files.
    - College Admissions, 1971
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 341)
  - General Files.
    - College Admissions, 1972
    - Department of Commerce--General
    - Department of Commerce--Business Development Conference
    - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights
    - Community Colleges--Virginia
    - Congratulations
    - Consumer
    - Corps of Engineers
    - Customs
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 342)
  - General Files.
    - C--General
    - Department of Defense--General (2 folders)
    - Department of Defense--Camp Perry
    - Department of Defense--Cape Charles NAVCOMFAC
    - Department of Defense--Cheatham Annex
    - Department of Defense--Coast Guard Reserve Training Center
    - Department of Defense--Army Air Mobility R&D Laboratory (USAAMRDL) (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 343)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--USAAMRDL (1 folder)
    - Department of Defense--Fort Eustis
    - Department of Defense--Fort Monroe
    - Department of Defense--Langley Air Force Base
    - Department of Defense--Naval Air Rework Facility, Norfolk
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 344)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--USAAMRDL (1 folder)
    - Department of Defense--U.S. Army Recruiting Command USAREC (Vol. 1)3
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 345)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Defense--USAREC (Vol. 2)
    - Denessy, Dr. Tyrone Z.--Cancer Cure
    - District of Columbia
    - Drugs
    - D--General
    - Eastern Shore District Office
    - Economic Development Administration--Commerce Department
    - Employment
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 346)
  - General Files.
    - Environmental Protection Agency [EPA]
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Air Pollution
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Water Pollution
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission [EEO]
    - E--General
    - Farmers Home Administration [FHA]
    - Federal Aviation Administration [FAA]
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation [FBI]
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission [FDIC]
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 347)
  - General Files.
    - Federal Highway Administration
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Maritime Commission
    - Federal Power Commission
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Trade Commission [FTC]
    - First District
    - Football Tickets
    - F--General
    - Gallery Passes
    - General Accounting Office [GAO]
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 348)
  - General Files.
    - General Services Administration [GSA]
    - Get Well
    - Gloucester County
    - Government Printing Office [GPO]
    - G--General
    - Hampton, City of
    - Hampton Institute
    - Hampton Office
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association
    - Port of Hampton Roads
    - Hampton Roads Sanitation District
    - Health, Education and Welfare [HEW] (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 349)
  - General Files.
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Food and Drug Administration [FDA] (2 folders)
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Office of Child Development
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Office of Education (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 350)
  - General Files.
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Public Health Services [PHS]
    - Health, Education and Welfare--Social Security Administration
    - Highways
    - Hopesville Ranch
    - House of Representatives
    - House of Representatives--Seniority System
    - Housing and Urban Development [HUD]--General (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 351)
  - General Files.
    - Housing and Urban Development--General (1 folder)
    - Housing and Urban Development--Sections 235 and 236 Programs
    - H--General
    - Immigration
    - Department of the Interior (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 352)
  - General Files.
    - Department of the Interior (1 folder)
    - Internal Revenue Service [IRS]
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Israel
    - I--General
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 353)
  - General Files.
    - Job Information
    - Department of Justice
    - J--General
    - Kennedy Center
    - K--General
    - Department of Labor
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 354)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Labor--Neighborhood Youth Corps
    - Lancaster High School
    - Leadership Program, 1971
    - Leadership Award, 1972
    - Library of Congress
    - L--General
    - Maps (2 folders)
    - U.S. Marine Corps
    - Marine Engineers Benevolent Association [MEBA]
    - Mariners Museum
    - Maritime Administration [MARAD]
    - Mathews County
    - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 355)
  - General Files.
    - Middlesex County
    - M--General
    - NASA
    - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities
    - National Park Service
    - National Science Foundation
    - Department of the Navy (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 356)
  - General Files.
    - Newport News, City of
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co., 1971
    - Newsletters
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration [NOOA] (sic)
    - Northampton County
    - N--General
    - Office of Economic Opportunity [OEO]
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness
    - Office of Management and Budget
    - O--General
    - Page School
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 357)
  - General Files.
    - Passes
    - Passports (2 folders)
    - Patrick Henry Airport
    - Patriotism
    - Patronage
    - Peace Corps
    - Peninsula Association for Retarded Children
    - Peninsula Regional Center for Mentally Retarded Children
    - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce
    - Post Office Department--General
    - Post Office Department--Commemorative Stamps
    - Prime Land Bank Corporation--Victor Forte
    - Bureau of Prisons
    - P--General
    - Recommendations
    - Redistricting Virginia, 1971
    - Retirement Letters, 1971
    - R--General
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 358)
  - General Files.
    - SALT Talks
    - School Children Letters
    - Securities Exchange Commission [SEC]--Dennison Smith--Rand Corp.
    - Selective Service
    - Small Business Administration [SBA] (2 folders)
    - Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area [SMSA]--Virginia
    - Department of State
    - Summer Employment--General (2 folders)
    - Summer Employment--Dell Flair
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 359)
  - General Files.
    - Supreme Court
    - Sympathy
    - S--General
    - Thomas Nelson Community College
    - Tours
    - Department of Transportation (2 folders)
    - Department of the Treasury
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 360)
  - General Files.
    - T--General
    - United Nations
    - University of Virginia
    - Veterans Administration [VA]
    - Viet Nam--General (2 folders)
    - Viet Nam--TND's Speech
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 361)
  - General Files.
    - Viet Nam--LT Calley (3 folders)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 362)
  - General Files.
    - Commonwealth of Virginia (3 folders)
    - Virginia--Constitutional Amendments, 1972
    - Virginia General Assembly
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company [VEPCO]
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science [VIMS]
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute [VPI]
    - Virginia Port Authority
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 363)
  - General Files.
    - Virginia Beach, City of
    - Virginia Beach Office
    - Visas
    - V--General
    - Wage and Price Freeze
    - White House--General
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 364)
  - General Files.
    - White House--Conferences
    - White House--Tours
    - College of William and Mary
    - Williamsburg, City of
    - Colonial Williamsburg, Inc.
    - Colonial Williamsburg--Reservations
    - Colonial Williamsburg--Visit of French National Assembly Friendship Group
    - W, Y--General (X and Z omitted) (2 folders)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, January-February 1971 (3 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 365)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, March-August 1971 (8 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 366)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, September-December 1971 (6 folders)
    - Invitations Regretted, January-April 1971 (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 367)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, May-October 1971 (7 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 368)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Regretted, November-December 1971 (3 folders)
    - Invitations Extended, 1971
    - Invitations Accepted, January-April 1972 (5 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 369)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, May-October 1972 (7 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 370)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Accepted, November-December 1972 (2 folders)
    - Invitations Declined, January-May 1972 (5 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 371)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Declined, June-December 1972 (8 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 372)
  - Invitations.
    - Invitations Extended, 1972
  - Legislation Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Possible Legislation by TND, 86th-92nd Congresses
    - Artificial Fishing Reef--Liberty Ships (P.L. 92-402, Sect. 3)
    - Bald Eagle Protection Act (P.L. 92-535)
    - Boundary Agreements Between Maryland, Virginia, and North Carolina (P.L. 92-565; 92-588)
    - Coastal Zone Bill (P.L. 92-583) (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 373)
  - Legislation Enacted, 1st Session.
    - Dismal Swamp and Canal (P.L. 92-478)
    - National Advisory Committee on the Oceans and Atmosphere
    - NASA--Convey Land to Chapel of the Astronauts (P.L. 92-227)
    - National Week of Concern for POWs and MIAs (P.L. 92-6)
    - Ports, Waterfront Areas, and Navigable Waters...to Promote Safety and Protect Environmental Quality (P.L. 92-340)
    - Technology Assessment Office (P.L. 92-484)
    - Wage Board Bill (P.L. 92-392)
  - Legislation Enacted, 2nd Session.
    - Academies--to Permit the President to Appoint...(P.L. 92-365)
    - To Amend the Fish and Wildlife Act (P.L. 92-502)
    - Passenger Vessels--to Authorize the Sale of (P.L. 92-296)
  - Legislation Enacted, General.
    - National Cancer Authority (P.L. 92-218)
    - District of Columbia--to Limit...Parking Tax
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 374)
  - Legislation Enacted, General.
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel--Yancey Disaster (P.L. 92-340) (3 folders) [see also Port--Pollution File]
    - Cruise Legislation (P.L. 92-323)
    - Pollution--Ocean Dumping (P.L. 92-532)
    - San Francisco Bay National Wildlife Refuge (P.L. 92-330)
    - To Facilitate the Transportation of Cargo by Barges Specifically Designed for Carriage Aboard a Vessel (P.L. 92-163)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, 1st Session.
    - Agriculture Exports (H. Res. 681)
    - Basketball--Merger of Leagues (H.R. 10211)
    - To Ban Sports Events from Closed Circuit TV (H.R. 7127)
    - Select Committee on the Elderly (H. Res. 158)
    - Farm Vehicles--Exemption (H.R. 8142)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 375)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, 1st Session.
    - Hansen, Oskar, III--Medal for Merit (2 folders)
    - Historical and Archaeological Data Preservation (H.R. 6258)
    - Israel--F-4 Phantom Aircraft (H. Res. 677)
    - MacLeod, Kenneth L.--Relief
    - Marston, Noel Scott--Relief
    - Mason, A. Hughlett--Relief
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - Mount Vernon--to Preserve Certain Lands in Maryland Shoreline Opposite Mount Vernon (H.R. 8038)
    - National Navy Wives Clubs of America Day (H.J. Res. 353)
    - Peace--to Authorize the Establishment of a Joint Committee (H.J. Res. 1237)
    - Peru--Denying Loan of U.S. Destroyer (H. Con. Res. 173)
    - POW--Humane Treatment--Geneva Convention (H. Con. Res. 112)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 376)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, 1st Session.
    - POW--Joint Committee on Treatment of (H. Con. Res. 18)
    - Silent Prayer or Meditation in Public Schools (H.J. Res. 981)
    - Rural Job Development Act (H.R. 10894)
    - Shore Restoration and Protection Projects (H.R. 9045)
    - Social Security--Remove Income Limitation (H.R. 8830)
    - Taxes--Exception for Monetary Awards Made by Federal Agencies (H.R. 12794)
    - Viet Nam Disengagement
    - Voluntary Wage and Price Limitation
    - Weinberg, Samuel E.--Relief
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, 2nd Session.
    - Endangered Species Conservation Act of 1969--Funding (H.R. 12986)
    - Funds Impounded by the President (H.R. 13379)
    - Firearm Act--Gun Control (H.R. 15790) (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 377)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, 2nd Session.
    - Gun Control (1 folder)
    - Holidays--to Amend Title 5...Memorial Day and Veterans Day (H.R. 14860)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - NASA--to Amend to Provide for Certain Additional Reports
    - Occupational Safety and Health Act--to Amend (H.R. 12296)
    - Soft Drink Franchise System (H.R. 13132)
    - Veterans Pensions--World War I Pension Act of 1972 (H.R. 15490)
    - Viet Nam--Bombing Escalation
    - Joint Committee on Environmental Quality (H.R. 15244)
    - Peru--Revoke Leases of Vessels... (H. Con. Res. 261)
    - Tax Exemption for Korean Servicemen (H.R. 10861)
    - Tax Return Forms--To Create a Joint Committee to Investigate... (H.J. Res. 662)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, General.
    - Coastal Corridor Highway
    - Public Health Service Hospitals--to Remain Open and Funded (H. Con. Res. 152)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 378)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, General.
    - Anti-Busing Amendments to the Higher Education Act (H.R. 7248) (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 379)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, General.
    - Anti-Busing Amendments (5 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 380)
  - Legislation Introduced and Failing Enactment, General.
    - Anti-Busing Amendments (6 folders)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, A-B (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 381)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, C-J (8 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 382)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, K-S (10 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 383)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, T-Z (X omitted) (6 folders)
    - 2nd Session, A-D (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 384)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, E-M (10 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 385)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, N-Z (11 folders)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - General--January 1971
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 386)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - General--February-December 1971 (11 folders)
    - Downing--January-February 1971 (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 387)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Downing--March-December 1971 (10 folders)
    - General--January-April 1972 (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 388)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - General--May-December 1972 (9 folders)
    - Downing--January-May 1972 (5 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 389)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Downing--June-December 1972 (7 folders)
    - News Releases
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 390)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Magazines with Tom Downing Articles, 1971
  - Office Accounts.
    - Office Equipment, Supplies, and Services
    - Flags
    - House Recording Studio
    - Office Personnel
    - Stationery Account, 1971
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 391)
  - Office Accounts.
    - Stationery Account, 1972
    - Subscriptions Account
    - Summary Statement of Accounts
    - Telephone and Telegraph Units
    - Out-of-D.C. Telephone Service
    - Out-of-D.C. Telephone Service--1st-4th Quarters 1971 (4 folders)
    - Out-of-D.C. Telephone Service--1st-4th Quarters 1972 (4 folders)
    - Transportation Expenses--E.M. "Tiny" Hutton
    - Transportation Expenses--Thomas N. Downing
    - District Office Expenses
    - District Office Lease File
    - Miscellaneous Office Expenses
  - Political Files.
    - Accomack County, 1972
    - Campaign, 1972--TND (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 392)
  - Political Files.
    - Campaign, 1972--General
    - TND Campaign Committee
    - Campaign Expenses
    - Campaign Reports
    - Congratulations
    - Contributors to TND Campaign
    - Contributor Lists (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 393)
  - Political Files.
    - Contributor Lists (1 folder)
    - Campaigns and Elections--Not TND
    - Clippings--State
    - Election Results, 1972
    - Essex County
    - Finance Committee
    - First District
    - Political Friends and Nice Letters
    - General (3 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 394)
  - Political Files.
    - Gloucester County
    - Hampton
    - Helpers in TND Campaign
    - House Leadership Fights, 1971
    - House Internal Politics and Elections
    - Campaign Issues
    - James City County
    - Kostel for Lt. Governor of Virginia
    - King George County
    - King and Queen County
    - Lancaster County
    - Local Elections and Democratic Party
    - Mailing Lists
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 395)
  - Political Files.
    - Mailing List--State Convention
    - Mathews County
    - Middlesex County
    - Materials to be Sent Out
    - Support of Wilbur Mills
    - Miscellaneous
    - National Democratic Party and Election
    - National Democratic Party Reforms
    - New Kent County
    - Newport News
    - Northampton County
    - Northern Neck
    - Northumberland County
    - Petitions
    - Pugh, John S., 1971
    - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures (2 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 396)
  - Political Files.
    - Requests for Political Information
    - Richmond County
    - Sanford for President
    - Scott Senatorial Campaign
    - State Democratic Party and Elections
    - State Politics--Virginia Young Democrats
    - Virginia Redistricting
    - Washington Friends
    - Wells, Dr. Kenneth--TND Opponent
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 397)
  - Political Files.
    - Wells, Dr. Kenneth--Clippings on
    - Westmoreland County
    - Williamsburg
    - Women for Downing
    - York County
    - Young Adults for Downing
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - A
    - Broad Creek, 1969
    - B
    - Chincoteague Inlet
    - Chisman and Goose Creeks
    - C (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 398)
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - C-F (4 folders)
    - Gathright Lake
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 399)
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - Rivers and Harbors General Information, 1969 (3 folders)
    - G
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 400)
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - H
    - Intracoastal Waterway--Chesapeake and Delaware Bay, 1969 (2 folders)
    - Intracoastal Waterway Luncheon, 14 January 1969
    - I-L (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 401)
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - M-O (3 folders)
    - Piankatank River, 1969
    - P-R (4 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 402)
  - Rivers and Harbors Materials, 91st-92nd Congresses.
    - S-Y (X and Z omitted) (7 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 403)
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files, January 1971-May 1972 (3 folders)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 404)
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files--June-December 1972 (2 folders)
    - Armed Forces Speeches
    - Commencement Speeches
    - Speeches on Congress--Duties, etc.
    - Dedications
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 405)
  - Speech Files.
    - Speeches on General Legislation
    - Maritime Speeches
    - Patriotic Speeches
    - Political Speeches
    - Space Committee Speeches
    - Miscellaneous Speeches
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 406)
  - Speech Files.
    - Miscellaneous Speeches, Undated, etc.
    - Extensions of Remarks, June 1970-October 1972, undated
    - Speech Material (1 folder)
- 92nd Congress, 1971-1972. (Box 407)
  - Speech Files.
    - Speech Materials (2 folders)
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (2 folders and 1 volume)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 407)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Academies--General Information
    - Air Force Academy--General Information
    - Merchant Marine Academy--General Information
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 408)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Military Academy--General Information
    - Naval Academy--General Information
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission--General Academy Information
    - Air Force Academy Appointees, Graduating Class of 1973
    - Merchant Marine Academy Appointees, Graduating Class of 1973
    - Military Academy Appointees, Graduating Class of 1973
    - Naval Academy Appointees, Graduating Class of 1973
    - Class Entering in 1973, Alvis-Kingston (26 envelopes)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 409)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Class Entering in 1973, LaMonica-Zeigler (44 envelopes)
    - Class Entering in 1974, Arnold-Butler (10 envelopes)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 410)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Class Entering 1974, Carruthers-Yuengert (53 envelopes)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 411)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agriculture
    - Agriculture--Appropriations
    - Agriculture--H.R. 16901--Appropriations
    - Agriculture--School Lunches
    - Appropriations Committee (2 folders)
    - Appropriations Committee--Expense Money
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 412)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Appropriations Committee--President's Budget
    - Armed Services Committee
    - Armed Services Committee--Appropriations
    - Atomic Energy Committee
    - Banking and Currency Committee (2 folders)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 413)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Banking and Currency Committee (3 folders)
    - Banking and Currency Committee--Mr. Ford's Inflationary Speech
    - Banking and Currency Committee--Economic Stabilization
    - Budget Committee
    - Joint Study Committee on Budget
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 414)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Committee on Committees--Committee Reform Amendment (3 folders)
    - Joint Committee on Congressional Operations
    - Select Committee on Crime
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - Joint Economic Committee
    - Education and Labor Committee (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 415)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor Committee (2 folders)
    - Education and Labor Committee--Appropriations
    - Education and Labor Committee--Appropriations--D. A. Holden
    - Education and Labor Committee--Collective Bargaining (H.R. 8677)
    - Education and Labor Committee--National Labor Relations Act (H.R. 1236)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 416)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor Committee--General Legislation
    - Education and Labor Committee--Minimum Wage (2 folders)
    - Education and Labor Committee--Vocational Rehabilitation
    - Education and Labor Committee--Office of Economic Opportunity
    - Education and Labor Committee--Pension Reform
    - Education and Labor Committee--Right to Work
    - Education and Labor Committee--Title I (H.R. 69)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (1 folder)
- 93rd Congress, 1973-1974. (Box 417)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (1 folder)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Appropriations
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--Atlantic Union
    - Foreign Affairs Committee--New Cambodia